Well, what a day!
Ta-da!
I'm coming to Yurikaze Konakada!
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Why did you come here?
Is it just the three of us?
Oh, the three of us? Now?
It's a nice atmosphere.
It's none of your business. You're a good friend.
I don't think it's any of my business.
I don't know, I'm just...
I don't know.
I just noticed that we're all here.
Well, this time...
This gentleman is here.
Please come in.
Hello.
I'm Hamada, the chairperson of the Murakata Fest executive committee.
It's been a while, Mr. Hamada.
It's been a while. Last year's Murakata Fest was a great success.
Thank you very much.
Subscribe to our channel!
You helped us a lot.
Not at all.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Thank you very much.
Why did you come to Yurix?
I thought it would be great if we could do it again this year.
Last year was the 10th.
I hope we can do something a little different for the 11th.
And we want to do it in a bust shape.
So we're going to Yurix in the shape of a breast.
Yes.
Maybe...
Maybe.
No, no, no.
I'm looking forward to it.
But, you know, last year, with the students...
Yes, that's right.
We had a lot of fun working together on the eco booth.
We want to expand this activity to the world.
We would like to expand the Eco-Booth activity to the world.
We are working to deepen exchanges between Japan and Korea.
That's great.
Sea of Korea
The Murakata festival is
It's over the ocean.
We're working on that initiative today.
It's like a prize for the Murakata Tourism Ambassadors.
We're going to have them go into that bay.
There's a bay within a bay, isn't there?
I'd like you to make it a big success.
It's a big responsibility.
The winner will decide whether this project falls over or not.
It's too important.
I'm counting on you.
I'll do my best to make it exciting.
Please do!
By the way, what you're working on today...
Is something being done?
Students from Japan and Korea will make curry.
It's like a curry battle.
Battle?
We're doing it in leaflets.
Thank you for watching.
Looks delicious!
Do you often eat beef curry in Japan?
Beef or chicken?
Trinh.
Chicken is good too, isn't it?
I've never had chicken curry.
Chicken curry?
I'll have chicken curry.
Okay? Chicken curry.
I love chicken curry.
You've decided on beef curry?
Yes, I'll have chicken curry.
What kind of curry did you decide on?
Japanese traditional house curry.
What's the best?
Wagyu beef.
Stop it!
Japanese Curry
Stop with the love!
I don't want to.
Wagyu, right?
Wagyu or Wagyu beef?
If we have enough.
I'll give it to you.
I'll make a curry with beef and chicken.
Beef and chicken curry.
Which is spicier?
Hot.
Are you okay with spicy?
Yes, I am.
You don't mind if it's a little spicy or not?
Hot.
Then it's not too spicy, is it?
Korean spicy food is...
Looks spicy.
Is it okay? I'll try my best.
I'll try harder.
Is it okay if I make it a week spicy?
Yes, it's fine.
What about using food coloring?
We're talking about making a blue curry.
Curry.
It's a little difficult to make a normal curry.
I was thinking of using a white curry or something.
If not, we can use stew as a substitute.
Like putting spices in a stew and making a curry.
Something like that.
So, it's a normal stew.
It's very adventurous.
Let's try it together.
I'm so glad we tried it.
Chocolate as a secret ingredient
Chocolate.
Are you sure? Just chocolate.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Are you okay?
What made you decide to use chocolate as a cab flavor?
Is it popular in Korea?
I've never heard of it.
Never heard of it.
Why did you decide to make the chocolate taxi-flavored?
Because this project is a curry challenge.
I'm willing to try anything.
Try
Try anything
Try anything.
I see.
I'm going for the blue curry.
Blue curry?
It's like we're both going for it.
Are you okay?
What kind of curry?
Chicken curry.
Chocolate curry.
Chocolate Curry.
So this guy is confident in his chocolate curry.
It's our secret, secret weapon.
A secret weapon.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Going with Japanese anime?Going with Japanese Anime?
Japanese Anime?
Shinnosuke
Crayon Shin-chan
What?
I knew it.
Chocolate Curry
It's really delicious!
I'll go get you a copy.
Imitation.
Yes, please.
Three, two, one.
Ho-ho-ho!
Hey, hey, hey. It's Shinnosuke.
What? Oh, my God.
That's great.
I can't make it. Can you support me?
Let's cheer! Let's cheer!
I'd like to be a cheerleader.
It would be nice if you could cheer me up.
I'll do it.
Love.
I'll do my best to make it more exciting.
I'm looking forward to it.
And one more thing.
There are Korean university students coming to Murakata Taisha Shrine.
I'd like you three to show them around.
I would like you to tell them about the beauty of Murakata.
What can you show them?
What? Korean?
No, I'm fine.
I'm a university student who understands Japanese, so I'll be fine.
If you learn to speak Korean...
What are your plans?
Thank you very much.
For now.
Three, two, one.
I was busy today.
I've got a guy from a developmental products company here.
I'd like to work with him.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Pleased to meet you.
Good morning.
Good morning. - Good morning.
We're the batten down the hatchet.
We are the Battenzions.
Good morning. - Good morning.
Let's get started.
Good luck.
Thank you for watching.
I'm really glad that you're doing this.
That's great.
Hey.
It's gonna be a... it's gonna be a beautiful day.
Oh, wow.
That's great.
Anything I can help you with?
No, I'm good.
I'm good.
Let's support them. Let's support them.
And I'm getting it from all over the place.
Why don't you just take this?
Sure, we should do it together?
Thank you very much.
What do you want me to get?
What kind of stuff?
Like this?
It doesn't look sharp.
Anything will do.
Thank you very much.
Can you cut it?
It's sharp.
Really?
Do you think I could twist it?
Do you want one of these?
Okay.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Wait a minute.
Listen to me for a second.
Listen to me for a second
Okay, okay
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's a blur.
It was shaky.
I don't want it.
No, no, no.
It's like I didn't get it at all.
Wait a minute.
Here.
Wood.
Is it hard?
Do you want hard wood?
What kind of wood do you want?
It's all right, it's all right, it's all right.
It's okay. It's okay.
Can I give him this?
You can have it.
Thank you very much.
You're early.
What's the Korean for "combo fire"?
Bull pioda.
Bull combo with fire is pioda.
Heh.
Bull is fire.
Yes, sir.
Heh.
I'm a bit of a manifan.
I don't talk.
I'm learning as I go
Heh.
Combo when you do a combo.
That way, right?
That way, that way.
Oh.
Wait a minute.
Okay, okay.
It's a bigger crowd than I thought.
Oh, excuse me.
Excuse me, sir.
Excuse me.
What's going on?
I feel like I'm used to this.
Now it looks like rampers.
Look around a bit.
Thank you for your time.
Do you cook?
I cook a lot.
What kind of sauce do you put on it?
We use a deep sauce with chocolate.
Do you usually cook?Do you usually cook?
I cook a lot.
Great. Enough about the enemy.
We're making a lot of progress while we're talking.
Do you usually cook?
We all do.
The boy who cut the meat for me before said he was making curry at home.
He was chopping onions.
Do you make curry at home?
He's making curry in Korea.
Thank you for your hard work.
Are you filming here?
We're filming here, right?
Yes, of course.
From the beginning.
I thought I'd throw my racket
I thought maybe you'd throw it in.
I'm throwing it in.
Oh, the manager's here.
Good morning.
Good morning
This is Ten-chan, the Murakata character.
We've been working with her, too.
Did you know that we've been there before?
Nice to meet you.
It's really nice to meet you.
I'd like to take your picture.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you, too.
Great. Here we go.
P.P.
Oh, my goodness! It's so creepy!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Can you take some pictures?
No problem.
I have no idea what the members are doing right now...
Sir, you know...
Is there actually a member in the audience?
Are there?
Take a picture, please.
Thank you very much.
I didn't realize you were here.
I'm so sorry.
You were already helping out earlier.
Oh, yeah, I helped you out.
I was so focused on the manager that I didn't even notice.
The manager is so cute.
The manager is so cute!
I made rice for...
Yeah, rice for 7?
Now...
I want some.
You look a little like Sakura's sister.
Oh, no.
I wasn't sure if you were my sister or not.
You've got a lot of visitors.
Are they coming? This way.
You're here a lot.
Have you done anything since you came to Japan?
I did!
Shopping.
Donkio?
It's nice.
Kenal City
What was its name again?
Clape.
Clape?
Clape. Delicious.
Yummy.
What is it? Clape?
Crape.
This...
Looks delicious.
Camamo.
Delicious!
And Japanese.
You speak Japanese?
Very well.
No, I don't.
Well, let me try one.
Gio, take one for me.
Mr. Unein Chair.
This is coming up because I'm translating.
Photographs.
One, two, three.
Oh, my gosh! Photographer!
Oh, this is it!
They're all in there!
Thank you so much!
It's so over! It's like the air is opened up!
It's like it's opening up!
Thank you very much!
What is this?
It's on YouTube!
Oh!
Look at this!
GUUUUUU!
GUUUU!
Come on!
Guuu-guuu!
Oh, no!
Oh! And, OK!
Okay, okay, okay!
What? How old are you?
Twenty-three.
The same age!
In Japan, I'm 22.
Oh.
I see.
You seem mature.
Oh, you didn't tell me, but honestly...
Ah, you know, I'm a bit lazy with words.
That's what she says.
Oh, yeah? I knew it.
Maybe if you put this in your food, it'll help.
It's soft.
How is it?
Is it hard?
Looks good.
It's hot.
No, it's hot!
That much?
Jumpy!
No!
Oh, no!
Put some water in it!
And it looks so good!
It's okay!
Thank you!
That's all I ate!
No good!
Not this one!
It's too hard!
Let's put some water in it!
It's hard!
Singal?
Too good!
Let's mix it some more.
Here you go.
So important.
Here you go.Yes, ma'am.
Good afternoon. - Good afternoon.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Are you cooking rice?
It's rice.
Do you eat rice? In Korea.
Yes, I do.
Did it take you long? To heat it up.
It took about three minutes.
Three minutes? That's great.
It's burning like crazy.
There's a lot of smoke.
Is this kind of thing common in Korea? We cook together.
We sometimes have fun with friends.
That's why I'm so good.
Can you introduce yourself?
I'd like to know.
I'm in the Ulm Baten Girls Club.
My name is Setasakura.
Cherry blossoms or flowers? Japanese flowers.
Three blocks.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Naa-chan?
Who's your Japanese idol?
I was born Mr. Zero.
And you?
Zero.
Then we might be the same age.
I envy you.
I'm so happy.
I need some great Japanese.
Do you know any Korean?
Like "kalkita kamunida"?
Oh, well, it's very beautiful.
Thank you very much.
Let's enjoy эксперспер Cheek!
Be my friend
Fighting for Poopy
You've seen it.
Already, a good pot of saucepan.
Idiot.
Just getting started
Like how to make it.
Raise your hand while you watch.
I'm looking it up on Instagram.
I'm looking it up on TikTok.
That's great.
Which one is it now?
It already fits.
Like TikTok.
Korea? TikTok?
TikTok, right?
TikTok.
They're cute.
I know, those girls just now...
There they are!
Oh, man!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Let's get some water in here!
He's not here.
Where is he?
Hey, is everything okay with your food?
What?
It's been sitting here all day.
I was talking about Luckey.
Oh, Luckey.
Oh, Lukki, he said the rice is in trouble.
Oh, I don't know.
The rice is in trouble.
It's been a long time since I put it down.
Is it okay?
Is it burnt?
It's hot!
Luki, do you have gloves?
I'm scared!
Oh! That's good!
Shovel, shovel!
Where's the ladle? It's right here!
Thank you!
Smells good!
Oh, yeah!
But, you know, the minute it's not stuck to you, it changes.
It's nice, isn't it?
Like in the middle.
I don't know.
It's hot!
Hot!
Hot, hot, hot.
Oh, no, it's hard.
It's hard.
I think it's okay.
I'll have it with curry.
Is it good? It's good!
Not good?
Yummy!
It's done!
It's done! It's done!
What is that aluminum foil?
That's a baked sweet potato!
A baked sweet potato?
We're making a crack in the foil by making a baked potato.
Cut a slit in it.
Then you put butter and honey on it.
And then pour butter and honey on it to make a sweet treat.
Wow!
Looks delicious!
Delicious!
Oh! Ddeokbokki?
Aaah! Delicious!
Amazing! Is tteokbokki made with soup stock?
Yes, it is.
Oh, I didn't know that! I had never heard of it before.
Do you make tteokbokki at home?
In Korea, I make it at school.
Oh, you make it at school?
Yes, I do.
With everyone in class?
Yes.
That's great.
Why did you decide to participate in this project?
Because there are not many opportunities like this,
There are not many opportunities to interact with Japanese high school students,
So I decided to participate in this program,
I've learned a lot of experiences by participating in this program.
It's amazing! You can't believe they are Japanese!
You are so good!
You can't believe how good you are!
You are amazing!
What are you baking?
I'm baking with eggs.
Like a scrambled egg?
Like that.
Looks delicious!
It's like the tostos they sell in Korean towns.
I see.
At food stalls.
That's right. Good luck.
Thank you. It's so cute!
The shrinkage...
The shrinkage. Delicious.
Oh, I see.
It's perfect already.
Is it going well?
It's great.
Shall we make it?You want me to make it?
Is that okay?
Can I make one round one?
Okay, sure.
I'll make one.
What did you make?
Onigiri in Korean.
Shmoppa.
Oh, that's right.
Wow!
This one.
Oh, Peru.
Can I go in?
Puedes.
That's about right, right? Maybe a little more?
Pork, right?
Pork?
Yeah.
This one, a little bit more?
A little bit more?
Oh, my God.
Is it great? Is it?
Oh, it's done!
It's done!
Yes!
Okay, let's eat later.
You sure?
Thank you!
Thank you for watching!
That's great!
I'm so happy for you, man!
Don't you feel bad?
Don't worry! I'll make it!
Say yes, guys.
You want to take a picture with me?
Yeah, let's take a picture together.
Do you want to bring your hand phone?
I'll get it.
I'll take the picture with you.
We'll take it together. We'll take it together.
You want to take a picture with me?
Why not?
Just the three of us. I'll start from here.
Four is fine.
Oh, man.
So cool!
See? All of it.
Here you go. Cheese.
I got it.
Thank you very much.
Me too.
Where are you?
Take me with you.
Just the two of us for now.
One, two, three.
Thank you very much.
Oh!
You speak Japanese?
I speak a little Japanese.
Very interesting.
Very funny.
Where'd you go for baseball?
How old are you?
I'm two.
Are you the same age?
We're friends.
Same age.
Have you ever been to this bank?
I went to the Monk Street in January last time.
I used to go there a lot before that.
But I couldn't make it.
You need to shop.
There are shrimp and octopus in it.
Shrimp and octopus, octopus too
I got it on rice.
Nakkoste, nakkoste.
Nakkoste.
I'm so happy.
Was it good?
It's spicy, isn't it?
Not spicy at all.
It's amazing!
I'm a freshman.
How old are you?
Sixteen.
You're young.
Free. Young.
Cute.
What's the latest fad?
Good luck. I'm looking forward to it.
I used to party.
Parties in the past, at school?
Yes, parties back in the day.
And watch the intramural soccer and baseball games.
You went to those.
And cheer for the team?
I have a boyfriend.
What team are you in?
Soccer.
I'll be there to watch.
That's right. I'm going to watch.
Who's your best friend?
The coolest guy.
Coolest guy in the whole year.
That's awesome.
Excuse me, is this the Buttercream Curry House?
Yes, ma'am.
That looks amazing.
Looks delicious.
Yes, it is.
It's so cute.
Please change your love.
I'll send you some from afar.
That's about right.
You can convey love, across the sea
I'm going to have a curry here.
I see.
Is that so?
Yes.
It's good.
That's good.
Can I have some, too?
No, it's fine. It's fine.
No, it's fine.
I won't eat if you do.
So that's how the system works.
Apparently.
It was like, "You can eat here gare.
I had to find my own place to eat.
It was pretty harsh.
Harsh.
Ai, do you promise to let us eat?
Yes.
He said he'd eat.
Curry from his place.
Thank you.
It's so good.
Did you sign the contract?
No, we didn't.
I still have to.
I haven't heard anything about it yet.
You should go see him again.
I've been to a lot of dental offices, but none of them have contracts.
Oh, no, no, no!
I'm going to lose my grant. - That's a lie.
You have to sign a contract.
Oh, my God!Eh, what shall I do?
Hee-hee-hee!
Green Curry
It was supposed to be green curry!
LOL!
What is this?
Looks bad!
You can't use coloring
Let's make a blue curry.
that's what we're talking about.
You put this in?
Yes, I did.
This is green.
What for?
Oh, my God.
It's actually green.
It's like a green curry.
It's actually blue.
Oh, my God.
I hope there's some left over for later.
A little bit of rice and...
May I have some of this curry?
May I?
Thank you very much.
There won't be any left over.
No, no, no, there won't be any left over.
Okay, then. Last but not least, the winning team.
This is one of the most sacred places in the precincts of this Murakata Grand Shrine.